Good morning! I thought I'll do a very very classy vlog for change and I just woke up to be honest.
I need to do my makeup. It's day two of the Amphifestival. I'm one of the presenters there and I have around about
an hour to get ready.
So let's go. Just doing my makeup a few years ago. I would have never ever
posted something of me without makeup.
It's a process.
And yeah, it's a quick and dirty makeup today, so to say, because it's day two of the festival.
Yesterday was already a full day and I'm tired.
So no experiments today, just playing safe with the makeup.
But I love being here.
Slept very good.
Alright, so packing my bag I need to bring or wear my first outfit.
That's that.
I also need to find some scissors at the venue because I still have the tags inside and it's
like in the middle of the bum.
Not that good.
Then I was thinking a lot about what to wear, what to wear and I decided to go with a catsuit tonight
and the harness. The harness is inside this bag
and here's the catsuit. So I need to bring that stuff with me for today because I won't go back
to the hotel anymore. And be prepared and don't forget anything. It's going to be a long day. I'll
probably be here again at 1 at night and it's now quarter past 10.
Got my first coffee.
This is the English vlog now?
This is the English... I do my vlogs in English but you can talk in German too.
I did not know that. Do you recognize why the face tracking thinks I'm Celine?
Do you know why? Celine probably... Do you see it?
Do you want to do it in English again?
Yes, we do exactly the same thing in English.
We do exactly the same thing in English. You're wearing my face thing.
Bindi. Because you stole it yesterday from where I left it.
Well, that's not stealing. You left it to anyone.
I saw it on your Instagram that you wore it. I had a selfie and I was like, aha.
That's very true. Do you know the meaning of the Bindi? We don't. Do you?
No, it was a fashion thing yesterday.
Probably.
And I took it off because it didn't fit my outfit anymore.
But you're not going to sweat today?
No.
Or will you? In the evening probably.
I don't know. I will change outfit in the evening because that's my thing to change outfit once a day.
Oh, I get it. Once a day?
Once a day.
Just once a day. At which time?
Somewhere in the afternoon.
Sometime in the afternoon.
You're not wearing a scarf.
Don't you think that your voice may be unprotected?
No, I don't know. Maybe. It's a bit rough already.
Your voice is already a little bit...
But I would be sweating if I would be wearing a scarf.
But you are usually wearing latex dresses in the summer.
And I would sweat too.
So I thought you would be used to be sweating by now, but you're not.
But I'm used to it, but if I don't have to why would I?
I get it.
Yeah.
What is your opinion on this matter?
Should Celine wear a scarf?
Yes or no?
Should she sweat?
I mean, it's all for you at the end of the day, right?
Yeah, definitely.
We do it for you.
Yeah.
Cheers.
So I'm sewing through my outfit because there are some pieces missing.
And, oh my God.
It's a mess.
like that
one or two mark chain one or two
You look very gothic today.
I don't know, I'm very colorful.
Not as fetish as usual or latex like.
Tonight, the cat suit is coming.
It's the one with the leather.
Thank you very much.
I have earrings today.
I thought it was make-up.
The earrings.
to announce the first band. So yeah, this is the outfit and we'll see how many people
are already here because it's quite early. First band starts at 11 so we have to be here
early too.
Who was at Covenant last time?
Some of you?
Not me.
You weren't?
I was on the ship.
I watched Pink Turns Blue. It was very nice.
No, I don't go on the ship. That's too scary for me.
I prefer to stay here. I'm safe here.
I like it better here.
Have you ever used 4711?
No, I used Patchouli again.
You were already with the next band.
What did you discover about them?
Motive Transylvania, I researched it of course, I'm prepared.
They were founded in 2014, they're from Italy.
I just disturbed them while they were doing their make-up when I asked them if they wanted a pre-production.
Did you give them any make-up tips? You can also say no.
No, I didn't give them any make-up tips.
The Wamba Gothen Rollies are doing industrial metal, that means we'll all be awake soon,
because it's getting hard this morning.
Do you have make-up rings or are they real rings?
They're real rings.
Thank you for your attention.
That's right!
Right!
Now we have more.
Do you have more information?
She describes herself as a very energetic live band.
We will ask you later if you think you were energetic and if you got energy.
Give the next band your energy.
She gives you her energy.
Ladies and gentlemen, Motor Transylvania!
Have fun!
Alright, it's breakfast time.
I'm having veggie hot dog for breakfast because I need to eat something.
I just announced the first band.
Here is Jens.
Come on.
Sorry.
This is Jens, one of my co-hosts.
going to announce the next band. So yeah, that's how it is.
I'm going to check on X-Size if they want to have an announcement.
Good morning everyone!
Hello!
Good morning!
No make-up!
Do you want me to announce your band?
Sure!
Yes, let's do that!
But do it good!
I'll try to, I'll give my best!
Do the best moderation you've ever done in your life!
Oh, oh, oh, man!
You can do it!
I believe in you!
Okay, okay!
How are you?
Are you ready?
We've tried to bring the musical genre to a change and we've managed to do it with electronic
and with a lot of humor!
So if you want to hear some more of the song, you're also welcome here.
Each song is a little bit different.
And you said you were here 13 years ago at the Amphi Festival.
Who was here 13 years ago?
Did you see them here?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8...
Who was here at every Amphi Festival?
Very good.
Very lucky.
Let's start.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Have fun and dance a night at X-Tide!
I'm still in the mood for love
Dear fans of Celine,
Celine is a little bit tired,
she has a huge tendency to rest her head on the table etc.
and I don't accept that.
The festival is nearly over, but you know,
we gotta keep the spirit high and just do something.
So this is why I dance a little, I usually don't dance,
but so that your favorite Celine is gonna wake up maybe even out of disgust.
I'm not saying it's a good dance but it's just probably making her more awake and aware of you,
her favorite fans, who she loves. Great job Marc, great job. Thank you very much.
All right, I am super tired. So energy drink it is. I don't know why I'm so tired.
No idea, but I changed outfit. This is the outfit because it's also colder, it
started to rain and yeah I'm just always planning two outfits per day. That's how it is.
We're here chilling and yeah just talked to Empathy Test if I should announce
them later. They said yes which I love because they're one of my favorite bands.
And now, let's go. I need to get awake again and wake up and be more energized.
So that was Empathy Test, the only full concert I saw today.
I just love them so I had to stay there and watch them.
And now I'm off to announce the next band and I think I'm getting cold.
Oh my god.
Jens, what are we doing now?
Ah, moderation!
Yes.
Joachim.
Please.
And a photo.
Are you happy already?
Yes.
Let's go.
Do we have no sound again?
Check, check, check.
That's not the...
Oh, sorry.
Check, check, check.
That's not the...
Ah!
I'm feeling alone, and colder than a stone.
Call me you know.
It's so nice being here.
I'm feeling alone, and colder than a stone.
Call me you know.
It's so nice being here.
I'm feeling alone, and colder than a stone.
Call me you know.
It's so nice being here.
I'm here at the Beach Club, which is my favorite location of the festival.
But it's just been raining.
That's why it's a bit empty.
But still, I love the fact that Goth people are sitting here at the beach.
And here's the Rhine.
That's really cool.
Is it beer o'clock?
Beer o'clock, mindestens one.
Mindestens one?
Yeah.
So we're just hanging out. It wants to follow you, your face.
My face?
Yeah, it follows your face.
Really?
Yeah.
Wow.
It's magic.
It's magic. Now it lost you.
It's the end.
Ah!
Now it's confused.
Hello?
Why are we speaking English?
Because my vlog is in English.
Oh, I didn't know.
Yeah, now you know.
Because I'm not very good in English.
No one noticed until now.
Okay.
I did it wrong.
No, you did fine.
What are we doing now? Announcing the last bands?
Your beloved Celine is announcing the headliner band which is a big honor for announcers.
So she's the head announcer so to speak.
And I will go to the second headliner band playing on the other stage called Welle Erdball.
This is the symbol of Welle Erdball. Highly fashionable. Also removable.
And what are you going to say?
Do you already know?
I don't know.
No.
I'm saying...
We have two minutes.
Oh, we have two minutes.
I heard.
Yeah.
So I don't know if I can spill the tea here, but I brought the whip because the singer
of the band that Celine is going to announce is getting whipped on stage and they didn't
have a whip.
But then Celine said she doesn't know how to whip.
Did you know that?
if you're thinking now then you know if you know you know you know yeah if you know you know
so but i think what celine usually does is before her announcement starts she goes into
contemplation like five minutes of meditation deep thoughts what what what there's nothing to laugh
there came laughter from the background um what what is your meditation technique
Close my eyes.
That's it.
Just close my eyes.
Wow, don't spill the tea again.
Also, what you don't know is,
probably you're asking yourself,
why is Celine standing a little bit tilted?
That is because her shoe died,
but she also cares
about her announcement, so with a defective shoe,
she's going to go on the
slippery stage.
I'm just going to hand off my microphone and camera to you
doing the video now.
nonsense okay but go ahead you say something
So I just announced Eisbrecher, the last band of tonight.
You can actually see them here at the screen.
And they gifted me their mascot, an ice beer.
I'm going to head to the front row I guess.
In Germany we would say Graben.
Let's go!
I'm not afraid of the dark
I have no fear of the dark
Cheers!
Hallo!
Danke!
Okay, I just arrived back at the hotel. It's almost one o'clock and I'm going to bed now.
I had a wonderful time. Tomorrow I will drive to Wacken Festival.
Don't ask me why.
Anyway, it was a great time, it was a great day. You could see
some sides of me without makeup, for example. I usually don't show. Let me know in the comments if you want to see more of
these kind of vlogging videos and have a good night.